Millie Poli

UX Designer - Design Researcher Sydney, NSW

About Me

I'm a User Experience Designer, passionate about research and problem solving.

Working previously as a Nutritionist, I built great relationships with patients and was able to deeply understand their behavior and motivations, and found solutions for each of their requirements to achieve the discussed goals.

Work Experience

Guardian Childcare & Education Chef/Nutritionist - JAN 2020 - JAN 2022

- Responsible for cooking classes and immersive cooking experiences
- Built relationships with parents and children creating a special environment and best experience during the children's stay at the Centre Utilizing empathy research, to help kids and parents make better decisions when

Mika Events - Luxury Picnics

choosing what to eat.

Founder/Manager - NOV 2020 - DEC 2021

As a founder, I conducted Market Research, Competitive and Comparative Analysis and Interviews to understand more about the Picnic Market and user needs.

I managed 3 employees, organized appointments and interviews with customers and facilitated end to end the process.

Industry Skills

Professional Skills

- Discover: UX Research
- Define: Synthesis
- Surveys
- Competitive &

Comparative Analysis

- Contextual Inquiry
- User Interviews
- Field Studies
- User observation
- Market analysis
- Affinity Mapping
- User scenarios
- Journey Mapping
- Personas & archetype
- User flows
- Information Architecture

Contact

- 0426 020 087
- millepolicamilo@gmail.com
- https://milliepoli.com/
- in https://www.linkedin.co/in/kamille-poli/

Education History

General Assembly - Sydney, NSW

UX Design Immersive

Full-time UX Immersive course with 500+ hours of

Jan 2022 - professional workshops.

April 2022 Developed in-class

projects practicing the design thinking process and design tools

Estacio de Sa University - Brazil Bachelor Degree in Nutrition

Jan 2010- Nutrition and dietetics skills,
JUL 2014 patient interviews and how
to achieve a healthier life.

Achievements

3 times winner "Guardian Gstar" Employee of the month

Guardian Childcare & Education

Design Tools

FIGMA MIRO SKETCH Trello

Ideation: Solution & Iteration

- Problem Solving
- Design Studio
- Sketchina
- Wireframe & Wireflows
- Usability Testing
- Prototyping

Deliver: Communicating with Client

- Presenting project
- Storytelling
- Feedback loops
- Product Analytics
- Working with a team